BC. TSIMAFEI MAROZ

tsimafei.maroz@gmail.com

+420776118241

L.

Brno, Czech Republic



In development I prefer ReactJS, Redux toolkit and TailwindCSS or CSS modules. At the moment I am focused on gaining new work experience, improving my skills and learning new technologies. You can see my works by following this link: https://timmrz.github.io/portfolio/

SKILLS

HTML

Advanced

CSS

Advanced

JavaScript

Advanced

ReactJS

Advanced

Tailwind CSS

Advanced

GIT

Skillful

TypeScript

Skillful

Redux Toolkit

Skillful

CSS3

Skillful

Bootstrap

Basic

LANGUAGES

Russian

Proficiency (C2)

Czech

Upper intermediate (B2)

English

Intermediate (B1)

INTERESTS OR HOBBIES

In my free time I am excited to play ping pong or billiards, and I also enjoy playing chess.

WORK EXPERIENCE

STUDENT OF FRONTEND COURSES

SKILLBOX / MAY 2021 - CURRENTLY

developing websites in HTML and CSS

developing responsive website layout

using BEM class naming

solving practical problems Javascript, DOM manipulation, creating interactive interfaces

developing applications in React, using React Hooks

using the State Manager and React Routing

using basics of NodeJs and npm

using CSS modules

WAREHOUSEMAN

ROHLIK.CZ / BRNO, CZECH REPUBLIC / OCTOBER 2018 - JUNE 2019

storage of goods

updating the information about the product in the warehouse in the database

picking and packing orders

EDUCATION

FACULTY OF BUSINESS AND MANAGEMENT

Process Management

Brno University of Technology / Brno, Czech Republic / 2018 - 2022

COURSE OR CERTIFICATE

PROFESSION FRONTEND-DEVELOPER

Skillbox / 2021 - 2022